WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Welcome to the White Lotus.
Happy to be here.
_
- We just got married
the day before yesterday.
Sounds like you scored. He's super rich.
Well, his family is wealthy.
I think you put us in the wrong room.
Maybe I should call my mother?
Why do you keep looking at your dick?
I'm looking at my balls.
Are they bigger?
I haven't seen them in a while.
- It's cancer.
- We have not gotten the results.
Nicole, it's the doctor.
She can't have a baby
the first day on the job!
Did you think that guy was hot?
What guy?
Fuck!
_
- Synced and corrected by Darrow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Does this suck?
Are you worried we're gonna get bored?
No.
I wish we had drugs.
I know.
I have weed.
- Holy shit.
- It's not very much.
I don't have anything
to smoke it with, though.
Oh, wait. What am I talking about?
I threw it in last minute.
Fucking legend.
Is your mom gonna freak?
Yeah, totally.
Do you wanna do a shotgun?
Yes.
We're gonna get fat.
This shit makes everything delicious.
Oh, shit. I have Addies
if you wanna be skinny tweakers.
I don't like taking 'em, though,
'cause then I can't sleep
and I get all jittery.
Oh, well, I...
I brought Ambien,
uh, Xanax, and a few Klonopin.
But we can't use it all
'cause I need them for my panic attacks.
Holy shit.
I totally forgot that I stashed
some ketamine in here, Paula.
We're so stacked.
Hawaiian K-hole.
I love it when you whisper.
Do you wanna do some ASMR?
Yeah!
Yeah! Oh, thank God.
The fuck?
Everything's fine.
Your dad just found out
he doesn't have cancer.
What?
Is something on fire?
No, uh, we're just doing witchcraft.
Making offerings to Hecate.
Oh.
Well, isn't it great news
about your dad?
He was convinced he's dying,
but he's gonna live.
Okay, great.
Can you guys go back to your spaces now?
Okay. Night.
Honey, the kids are so happy.
I just told them, and they're thrilled.
Can I get a hit?
No.
I'm telling Mom that you're doing
bong rips in the room, then.
Don't be a little bitch.
Snitches get stitches.
Where were we?
So, what's going on? How's Lani?
Who's Lani?
Wait. Are you serious?
The trainee that had a baby
in your office.
Yeah. She's, um...
She's at the hospital.
I think she's okay.
How's the baby?
Well, if it had died,
I think I would've heard.
Are... Are you okay?
I was criticizing her all day,
and she was in fucking labor.
Last night, I wanted a drink
so fucking bad.
Uh-uh.
Listen, you are five years sober.
You don't wanna mess with that.
Yeah, but what if I just
can't fucking do this anymore?
You're gonna get it together. Okay?
You still got some gas
in the tank, right?
Aloha.
This is Mr. Ferrer,
in the Bredford suite.
Yes, Mr. Ferrer, how can I help you?
The treble on my TV is too high.
Just go.
I need it removed from the sound bar.
Uh-huh.
Girls.
Let's get going.
You don't wanna miss breakfast.
Mom, you can't just open the doors.
Why not?
Paula's an HSP.
What is that?
Highly sensitive person.
That's not real.
Mom, it's a clinical diagnosis.
Really? Who's her physician?
Lena Dunham?
It's real.
Yeah, you could inflame my Morgellons.
We don't want that. Sorry, Paula.
Next time I'll knock.
Morning, ladies.
Oh, good, honey. Let's get breakfast.
Okay.
What the hell?
Quinn, why are you on the floor?
There's no air in here.
Olivia.
What?
Your brother is stroking out
in the kitchen.
What? Dad, what the hell are you doing?
- You're so beautiful.
- Ugh.
You're so smart.
Don't you think?
- Yeah.
Guys! Ugh, this is...
Is that a water bong?
Hey, did you guys bring pot
on the plane?
- We found it on the beach.
- It's prescription.
Yeah, what... what are you,
opening a Mexican pharmacy?
It's prescription.
They were partying all night
and making weird lesbian noises.
- Ugh.
- We weren't being lesbians, Dad.
Yeah, we were being sea hags.
I think this might be better over here.
Uh, okay. Hey, sweetie.
I thought I had cancer, but I don't.
Yeah. I just have an abnormal
reaction to a virus.
That's great.
Yeah! So I have a...
like a new lease on life.
You're not getting rid of me yet, kid.
Why'd you think you had cancer?
Well, if you really wanna know,
Paula, my testicles are swollen.
- Swole balls? Really?
- Yeah.
Did they biopsy your balls, Dad?
No, just an MRI.
Are they still big?
Have they deflated yet?
Not yet.
So if it's a virus, are you contagious?
If we caught it what would happen to us?
Will our clits explode?
That's a nauseating image, Olivia.
Honey, what are you doing?
I'm cleaning up.
No, you're rearranging the hotel room.
No, I'm improving our space.
Stop moving furniture, Nic.
We're here for a week.
I need nice feng shui.
Dad, she's having another manic episode.
Oh, good.
Okay. Let's go guys,
let's go to breakfast.
- Quinn, get your clothes on.
- Mom, it's vacation!
It's a breakfast buffet in Hawaii!
It shouldn't be a stressful situation!
Does he have to slam every door?
What?
Love ya, bud.
Hey.
Buffet is decent.
What is it?
I just got an offer to do a piece.
Ah, you're on your honeymoon. Fuck that.
Yeah.
Does it sound good?
Oh, it's, um, about a YouTube influencer
who sponsored
a Get Out The Vote campaign.
And then he took the five winners
to Burning Man in a...
an electric RV that can actually
hover above the ground.
What? Fuck that.
Yeah.
But he got 80,000 teenagers
to register to vote.
What are they gonna pay you?
A few hundred dollars.
No way. Tell 'em no.
Well... Thank you.
I can't say no.
If I keep saying no, then they're...
they're not gonna come to me anymore.
Like, if I want assignments,
then I... I need to stay in the mix.
Yeah, but what?
You're on your honeymoon.
You're gonna hole up in the hotel room,
just write some disposable garbage?
It's not garbage.
Yeah, fine, but it's like...
it's like so many
of the assignments they give you.
It's just clickbait
gussied up as some, like,
high-minded trendy woke bullshit.
Plus, what does it matter
if they stop calling?
You don't need the money.
Yeah, but I spent years of my life
building these relationships.
Look...
You did those jobs for dough. Right?
'Cause you needed the work. And...
I don't know,
I hate to, like, blow your mind,
but your situation has changed.
Like, you don't need
to do anything anymore.
Now you just do what you wanna do.
And whatever that is.
Well, that's very generous of you.
You're my wife. Come on.
You must've thought about this.
The reality of that's, like,
hard to process, you know?
Like, my parents were always broke,
and I haven't spent
a day of my life, Shane,
where I wasn't hustling
or generally just worried about money.
Welcome to the rest
of your wonderful life.
I'll be right back. 'Scuse me.
Hey, excuse me. Hey, buddy. Excuse me.
Ah, Mr. Patton.
How are you this morning?
Yeah. Okay.
So I have this email here,
forwarded from my mother.
Oh, an email from your mother.
Okay. Okay.
So, yesterday you said that we paid
for the room that we have.
But actually we did pay more money
for the room we don't have. So...
I assure you,
your mother is only paying
the rate for your current room.
Right.
You guys made a mistake.
Okay? So just...
just own up to your mistake,
it's all I'm asking.
Well, if there's been a mistake,
I do apologize.
I'm so very sorry.
Thank you.
Um, mistakes happen, you know,
but I'm just on my honeymoon,
you know, and, uh,
it's just not the kind of trip
where you wanna be impacted negatively
by someone else's mistake.
Oh, of course not.
Right, so, I guess
I'm just wondering what, uh,
you might be able to do for us
to make us feel better
about the whole situation?
Well, as I told you yesterday,
the Pineapple Suite is occupied.
Right. When are they leaving?
The Volkmers are departing
the day before you, on Wednesday.
And due to our new cleaning policy,
there would not be enough time
to get you in there.
Okay. Um...
Do you think we can get
another kind of upgrade?
Well, you and your wife
are in the biggest suite.
Besides the Pineapple Suite.
There is another suite
in the same category,
with a slightly bigger floor plan
- because it has a second powder room.
- Okay.
I could see if it's available.
Would you like a second toilet?
Yeah. Great.
Yeah, it's a garden suite,
so no ocean view,
but it does have that second toilet.
Um, no. That's...
That's... that's all right.
Look, you are a valued guest,
Mr. Patton.
And I sense your frustration.
Yeah.
Since I can't get you
the other room, um,
I am hopeful there's some other way
we can make this up to you.
Let me think on it, okay?
You go enjoy your day.
- Okay.
- And I'll come find you later.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
All right. Thanks.
Ooh.
Belinda...
You...
you, you're so good at this.
Feeling better?
Oh my God.
Was that really 90 minutes?
'Cause, oh my God,
it... it felt like ten.
I think you fell asleep.
Oh my God.
I know I fell asleep because I...
I dreamt that I was on the top
of this beautiful
mountain range in Asia.
Oh, that's cool.
And I had a cyanide pill.
And I just...
Listen, you... you are so talented.
Thank you.
You know, most people,
they really don't know
what they're doing.
You know, they...
they lie you down and...
and then you just get lubricated.
But... you...
you really know where you're going.
Do you think you could have dinner
with me at the hotel tonight?
Come on. 'Cause I woke up
this morning and I swear to God,
I felt better today
than I've ever felt in my life,
and I just really need to know
how you did that.
The hotel doesn't really like it
when the staff interacts
with the guests in that way.
What do you mean? You can't have dinner?
It would be unusual.
Like some kind of caste system?
Tanya, thank you so much
for the invitation.
I really appreciate it.
That's absurd.
We can have dinner. Who do I to talk to?
You know what? Um...
I'll talk to Armond,
and I'm sure it'll be fine.
Yeah, it will be fine. Yeah.
Um, I get off at 7:00.
Yeah, that's good.
I mean, like a couple minutes after 7:00
at the... at the restaurant.
Sounds great.
You guys have like nachos?
You wanted the aloha nachos?
Uh, yes.
Aloha nachos comin' up.
Ah, ja.
Ja, ja, ja. Uh-huh.
- Ja.
Well, I'm sure I'll see you around.
- It was nice to meet you.
- See you later.
- Auf wiedersehen.
- Tschüss.
Who are they?
Ah, it's the German couple
that's staying in our room.
Mm.
He's a fucking liar.
The husband?
No, the... no, the fucking dude
at the fucking front desk.
You said he apologized.
Yeah. He told me the Germans
were leaving Wednesday
so we wouldn't have enough time
to switch rooms and get in there.
They just told me they're flying
back to Hamburg on Tuesday.
Well, then we can get
into the room on Tuesday.
What's the big deal?
Uh, he lied.
Well, maybe he just got it wrong.
No. He does not want us
to have that room.
Why wouldn't he want us
to have the room?
Why would he care?
I bet because he thinks I'm an asshole.
Well, were you an asshole?
No.
No, I was actually trying
to not be an asshole.
But you failed?
I'll call my mom,
see if they refunded the difference
between the rooms.
Honey? Hi.
Hey, Mom. What's up?
Okay, so the situation
with the room is not resolved.
- No.
- Can you check and see
if you got a refund
from the White Lotus?
Let's just call Lorenzo.
Who's Lorenzo?
The travel agent, sweetie.
We always use him. He's a shark.
Yeah, yeah, get him in on it.
- Should I?
- Yeah, why not.
That's what travel agents
are for, right?
He'll deal with it.
She's gonna have Lorenzo call.
They're gonna regret this.
Lorenzo is a gay Filipino beast.
Hey!
Ooh.
Quinn, come on.
Let's cut down on the screen time, okay?
Come on. Look around.
Isn't this place gorgeous, huh?
Yeah? How lucky are we, huh?
You know, when I was your age,
my dad died.
One of the great sadnesses of my life
is that you two never got the chance
to know each other.
Dad, can I, um, save my game
so I don't lose my score?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
He was like a real alpha, you know?
He was tough.
He was tough on me.
I worshipped him, you know?
He was a good man.
You know, when I thought I had cancer,
I told myself...
You mean yesterday?
Yeah.
Life's too short.
You gotta make the most
out of every moment.
You know, we've got to make
the most out of every moment.
Yeah, but with each other.
So I signed us up
to get certified in scuba.
No.
Yeah, come on.
It's like eight hours in the pool.
Eight hours?
Yeah, but then we get
to go out in the ocean!
Dad, that's gonna suck so hard.
No, come on.
Look, I wanna do this with you, pal.
Like, my dad was like this sportsman
and we did all this
active stuff together.
I never passed that on to you, okay?
So let's... let's mix it up,
let's bro out. Come on.
Okay, fine.
- What?
- Fine.
Yes?
Fine.
You make me so happy.
Sorry, am I interrupting?
Uh, it's fine. Hi.
Hi. I just wanna say hi. Um, I'm Rachel.
Oh, hi, Rachel, I'm Nicole.
I know who you are. Nicole Mossbacher.
- Can I... uh, do you mind if I sit?
- Please.
Yeah. Thank you. Thanks.
Hi, I'm sorry,
I hope I'm not disrupting your work.
- I know you have a huge job.
- Oh.
I'm... I'm answering emails,
and they know I'm on vacation.
Great.
- Um, are you on your honeymoon?
- Yes.
We saw you and your husband on the boat,
and you had that newlywed glow
about you, congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm, actually,
I'm having a little career crisis,
and I, uh, saw you working over here,
and I... I just wanted to say
that I admire you,
and you've just accomplished so much,
and, as a woman, it's...
it's really... it's inspiring,
so I... I... I just wanted
to tell you that.
That's very sweet.
Sure.
What's your career crisis?
Oh, I don't know, um...
It's a long story but,
uh, you know, I just...
I've been hustling my whole life,
and I've made inroads,
and it's not, like, the best career,
but it's not nothing either, you know.
Um, but Shane, my husband,
he's from this very, very wealthy family
and he's very successful,
like way more than I am.
And I just sometimes feel like...
I worry that his orbit is...
is stronger than mine and that, like,
I don't know, that, like,
his gravitational pull
is gonna, like,
just suck me in and, um...
Like you'll become a moon to his planet?
Yes, and not only lose
my mediocre career,
which is whatever,
but also, like, myself.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Do you know what I'm saying?
May I ask? Did you sign a prenup?
Yes.
But it's, you know, generous but...
But if your marriage ends,
you're not set for life?
No. I mean,
there's like a structure to it,
and a time component,
and it's like complicated,
but basically no.
Then I think you've got to be
really careful.
And you've got to keep
your own orbit going.
Because you don't want
a few years down the line
to have abandoned your career,
and I'm not saying
this is gonna happen to you,
but marriages don't always work out.
Especially because you seem to be
a smart and appealing young woman.
Thank you.
Your power is your independence.
Don't give up your power.
Okay.
Well, thank you so much
for talking to me.
Women have a lot to navigate.
And I just think it's really important
to support women when I can.
That's awesome.
Well, I won't bother you any more,
but thank you so much.
My pleasure, Rachel.
What do you do, by the way?
Oh, I'm, um... I'm a journalist.
- Ah, amazing.
- Yeah.
What outlet?
I'm freelance,
so all over the place, but, um...
I actually...
I wrote a profile about you.
I mean, not just you,
uh, also, you know...
It was, um, "Ten Power Women
in the Tech World."
It was for, uh, Business World.
You wrote that?
Yes.
You're kidding.
Mm-hmm.
That was a fucked-up piece.
What?
Yeah, I remember that.
That was a hatchet job.
Well, it was a puff piece.
Are you being serious?
I... it said you were kicking
the corporate world's ass.
No, you made it out like
I got my promotion because of optics.
"She rode the Me Too wave."
Bullshit like that.
Well, I couldn't not mention
the lawsuits.
But you didn't have
to make me come across
like I was some kind
of Machiavellian gorgon
using the victimization
of the other women in my company
just to further my own craven ambitions.
It didn't read like that.
I mean, that's the kind of thing
that hurts me,
not to mention the cause.
Well, I didn't think that, I mean...
It...
I was just basically repurposing
the profile of you from The Post.
Well, then that's bad journalism.
Not to mention, inaccurate.
I mean, I climbed
a hellish ladder on my own,
working my ass off.
I didn't ride some wave.
Well, I...
I'm sorry
that you didn't like the piece.
I don't know what else to say.
Well, have a nice vacation.
- Have a nice vacation, Rachel.
- Yeah. Have a nice vacation. Okay.
You sure you wanna do this?
I don't know. How long does it last?
Like twenty minutes.
Then yeah, definitely.
Here.
Oh my Lord.
Right?
Thank you for bringing me here.
You have no idea
how happy I am you're here.
Oh, fuck.
What?
Oh, fuck. Look. Oh, no.
Hey. Hi, girls.
Hello! Hi.
Hey. Hi.
How are ya? Having fun?
Oh my gosh.
Both of you are so pretty.
I've never seen you this close. Wow.
Look at your skin! Oh my gosh.
You have the most beautiful skin
I've ever seen.
Really, like the dewy skin
that athletes have,
like, after a race,
like, just... but it's natural.
Anyway, don't mind me,
'cause I'm here... I'm...
I'm just scouting right now.
I have a bunch of ashes
that I need to throw in the ocean.
I'm just looking for the perfect spot.
My mother passed away
a couple weeks ago.
She was in bad shape
for a very long time
and, uh, she loved the ocean.
That's why I brought her with me.
It's a heavy box.
You know, I just don't think
that I'm gonna be able to toss the ashes
right there on the shoreline like that.
What if she just splashes
back onto the beach?
It would be like littering.
I think I wanna charter a boat
and just bring her out into, like,
the deepest part of the ocean...
way, way out into the deep,
and sprinkle her very thoroughly.
What do you think?
We got... we gotta go.
Yeah. We have to pee really, really bad.
I know, I have to pee
but I'm not... I'm holding it.
So sorry about your mom.
Well, have a nice day, girls.
Hey!
Girls, you left your...
Do you know who you're dealing with?
His father is Peter Patton.
You have to make this right.
I send all my clients
to the White Lotus.
I've given you loads of business.
I know Randy Zeoli personally.
I'm taking care of it, sir, I told you.
I will call Randy Zeoli.
I'm giving them freebies.
They'll be in the room by Wednesday.
I thought the Germans
were leaving Tuesday.
We have our cleaning protocol.
Oh my God. Fuck your protocol.
We'll get them in as soon as we can.
I have to go now, I'm afraid.
Tuesday.
Fuck my ass! What?
Some lady found this
on the beach and gave it to me.
I was gonna put it
in the lost and found.
What, no tag?
No.
You all right, boss?
I'm busy. Anything else?
Nope.
This is Christie.
Yes, uh, Christie,
we need to send flowers
to Lani's room
at the hospital right away.
Okay. Do you want me to call
Tropical Florists or Nana's or...
No, just have one of the girls
do an arrangement
and a valet can drop it off.
Okay.
And what should we say on the card?
It doesn't... On the card, just write,
"Love and well wishes to you and..."
Do we know the name of the baby?
No, but I could call
the hospital to find out.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Um, just "Love and well wishes
from Armond and all your friends
- at the White Lotus."
- Today?
Yeah, and let me know
when it's delivered. Thank you.
Have you seen our bag?
It's like a green bag.
No, sorry.
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
I don't see it, it's not here.
Olivia, fuck!
Where were you guys?
Paula lost her backpack on the beach.
It's got some crucial shit in there.
What kind of crucial shit?
All of my thoughts...
for the thesis that I'm about to write.
- Ah.
- Oh.
- Already working on your thesis?
- Hmm.
That's impressive. What's it on?
Um, colonialism.
Oh, big topic.
That's why we need to find the backpack.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
That pretty girl
who was on the boat with us
was at the pool today.
She said she was a fan.
Of who?
Of me.
It was nice to hear,
although she's a terrible journalist.
So, I think I'm gonna take the job.
What? Oh, you're joking.
I think I should do it.
You're gonna write an article
about a floating RV at Burning Man
while we're here?
I just... I can't just walk away
from my career, Shane.
No one's asking you to walk away
from your career.
We're on our honeymoon.
Why are you so angry?
I'm not angry, I'm...
'Cause it's fucking weird.
You haven't worked
for like the last couple months.
I was dealing with the wedding,
and exactly.
You're gonna take a job
while we're here?
That, to be honest, it's...
That's rude. Okay? So, no.
No.
I just think it's funny
that I'm a role model to strangers.
But...
But what?
Most people admire
people who achieve things,
but you somehow look at it
as if it's a personality disorder.
Making shit happen all the time
is a compulsion.
It staves off feelings of emptiness.
Or whatever. Okay.
The real question is,
what exactly are you getting done?
Putin is an overachiever.
He's impressive, also evil.
Liv, your mother is not Putin.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
She runs one of the most profitable
search engines in America.
And she's made it as a woman
in a male-dominated culture.
It's very cool.
And her company is a part
of the unraveling of the social fabric.
Should I be rooting for that
just because it's run by a woman?
No, you should be rooting for that
because it's your mother.
Shane, you can't say no.
Shane, it's my decision.
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
You're gonna ruin our fucking honeymoon.
Is that what you wanna do?
Ruin this whole thing?
Mr. and Mrs. Patton, good evening.
I come bearing gifts,
a complimentary bottle
of Veuve Clicquot. May I pour?
Thanks.
Wonderful.
I am so very sorry
for all the confusion...
and I am determined
to get you into the Pineapple Suite
before you leave.
There we are.
Please enjoy.
Travel agent must've called.
Finally getting some respect.
I'm gonna go see
if anyone's found our bag.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Where's the lost and found?
Lost and found?
My friend, she lost her backpack today
on the beach out front.
It's green. I was just wondering
if someone turned it in or...
- I can check in the office.
- Okay.
There's a lot
of important things in there.
I'm sure. I'll take a look.
No luck, I'm afraid.
But we'll definitely keep an eye out.
Yeah. Keep an eye out.
All right.
I always thought it would be cool
to bring people instant relief.
I just... I really have
so much respect for what you do.
Thank you.
Are you enjoying your shrimp tacos?
They're really good.
This is so nice.
More than dinner, it's nice to get such
positive feedback, you know?
It's nice to know
you're really making a difference
'cause sometimes, I question that.
Why would you ever question that?
Well, the clientele here
is mostly rich white people,
and to be honest, I struggle with that.
Oh.
Okay. How about this?
Whatever they're paying you,
I'll double it.
You can get paid to have fun
on your honeymoon, with me.
I do think that there's a purpose
in helping even rich people, you know?
Helping them to find healing,
making them feel more present,
- more aware.
- Yeah.
Because rich people,
they're the ones that, you know...
are fucking up the whole world.
Yeah. I mean, I know a lot of rich,
white, fucked up people.
They could really use you.
Have...
Have you ever thought about starting,
like, your own business?
Come on.
No, because I would be down
for funding something like that.
- That's...
- You have a beautiful family.
- Oh!
- Oh, thank you.
I know. Yes, I... I know.
I'm the lady from the boat.
I saw you guys.
That's right. Yes.
And this is Belinda,
she works in the spa.
- Hi.
- And she's just incredible.
I mean, I was in agony yesterday
and I woke up this morning
and I had no pain at all.
Great. Oh, good.
I'll make an appointment.
Of course, yeah.
If she's not booked with me.
Okay.
Well...
I could be your publicist.
Where were you?
Bathroom. What'd he say?
He's gonna look into it.
Everyone...
Sorry. I don't know why I just stood up.
Uh...
This may be a little cheesy.
But, um, I just wanted to say...
that I had a little health scare...
and it turned out to be a real blessing,
because it's the kind of thing
that gives you
a new perspective on life and...
and how lucky we all are.
And when you really
think about it, I mean...
we have no problems.
We've got food to eat, family,
we're healthy and alive.
And when you think about how...
That... that family...
is so obnoxious.
The mother is a bitch.
And the daughter is a bitch also.
Never take anything for granted.
It's also a reminder
to look at things in a new way,
and if you do, then, like,
every day can be a new day, right?
And if it is...
it's like you're al...
you're always being born into life...
like, all the time.
You're not stuck...
decaying or dying.
Anyway, that's just
what I was thinking about.
I just wanna share it and... just...
I love you guys.
That's so sweet, honey.
Quinn. Quinn, just...
Oh, you know what?
Actually, I think I got it.
Okay. Oh, yes.
Mom, what are you doing?
Your brother is gonna suffocate
if he sleeps in the kitchen.
So get him his own room.
- Olivia.
- What? You can put a fan in there.
No. This is perfect.
This is fine. You sleep here.
You girls be nice.
Good night.
We don't want you in here.
Fine.
I'll just sleep on the fucking beach.
That was easy.
Who's the guy?
What guy?
The guy you were with
by the lobby. I saw you.
Just some busboy, I don't know.
Seemed like you knew him.
He's just some random
who tried to pick me up.
Hmm.
There. I emailed them and I told them
that I'm on my honeymoon
and I cannot do the piece.
Are you happy?
Yeah. Thanks, baba.
Yeah. Whatever. Whatever.
Hey.
You know what I'm gonna do for you?
Hmm.
Because I love you so much.
I am gonna give you
what every girl in America wants,
apparently.
A trip to Burning Man in an electric RV
that can levitate above the ground.
I love my wife.
My wife is so hot.
- Stop.
- I love my wife.
My wife is so hot.
My wife.
You're my wife.
Just give me a second, please.
Mm-hmm.
Hello?
Mark? It's your Uncle Charlie.
Hey, Uncle Charlie! How are you?
Well, you know, no big complaints.
- Same old shit, you know.
- Yeah.
I saw you called me.
Yeah, um, I'm actually in Hawaii
with the family.
- Hawaii, great!
- Yeah.
Son of a bitch.
Yeah, it's good. It's great.
It's really nice to get away.
Um, yeah, I called.
I had this health scare
and I thought I might have cancer.
Cancer, no.
Yeah. No, I... but I don't. I'm fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
But, um...
Oh, that's good, Mark. Good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I called because I was worried
and I just, you know,
I couldn't... I couldn't remember
what kind of, uh, cancer,
um, Dad had.
Cancer? What...
what... what type of cancer?
Yeah. Yeah, the cancer that killed him.
Well, Mark,
your dad didn't die of cancer.
What? Wait.
He... he didn't? I...
I thought for sure
that he died of cancer.
No, Mark,
your dad didn't die from cancer.
Okay. What did he die from?
He... he died from AIDS.
What?
AIDS?
Are you serious?
I mean... wait, are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure, Mark.
Okay, well... how did...
how did I not know this?
Well, your dad didn't want
anyone to know.
And you were young.
Your mother couldn't handle any of it.
But I thought maybe at some point
someone had told you.
No. No, this is...
This is the first I've heard of this.
Um, I... wait.
I don't understand. How did he get AIDS?
Well... well, by having sex with men.
Your father, Mark, he had sex with men.
He did?
He had two lives.
He had his family,
and then he had another life
with homosexuals.
What the fuck?
- Synced and corrected by Darrow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Your dad found out his dad
was having sex with other men.
- He could've been butch, Dad.
- Please.
- Maybe he was a bossy bottom.
- No!
Maybe Grandpa was a power bottom.
Does that make you feel better?
_
We need to find the backpack.
I checked lost and found,
it wasn't there.
I do hope we find it.
I want to do something romantic.
What about candlelit dinner
on our charter boat at sunset,
dolphins leaping
as you cruise the coastline?
Perfect.
Quick question.
What's going on with this lady?
Right.
I thought I knew my father.
Meanwhile, he's off getting manhandled
by some random dudes.
What's it like? Does it feel good?
Do you want to find out?
_
- Tanya gets these incredible
treatments from Belinda
and she just sees her as this
magician, healer.
And she starts to really
obsess about her
in a sense that she thinks
that maybe this woman is, like,
the key to getting rid
of all the pain of her life.
And in the second episode,
she has this idea
that Belinda should have
her own wellness center.
That's a way for Tanya
to keep her locked in.
Have you ever thought about starting,
like, your own business?
Come on...
I would be down for funding
something like that.
She improves
so quickly that she realizes
that Belinda's a genius,
and that Belinda shouldn't be stuck
behind a counter in some hotel spa
when she should have her own business
and be a superstar.
And I think she does want
great things for Belinda.
But I think she's a woman with ADHD,
so I think a lot of things
get in the way
with promising things to people,
when you can barely deliver
for yourself.
- You... You are so talented.
- Thank you.
Because of her privilege,
she doesn't understand
that gratitude can be expressed
outside of money.
She's just having
this super cathartic moment
with a really authentic person,
and authenticity,
especially at certain levels of class,
is not necessarily prevalent.
I am so very sorry
for all the confusion.
Here we are.
Please enjoy.
Travel agent must've called,
finally getting some respect.
In episode two,
Shane gets the travel agent
to call Armond that he's under pressure
to fix this mistake that he's made
and trying to make it right
with this guy who's on his back.
And then he's got real addiction issues,
and this bag of pills lands in his lap.
He could disappear
and nobody could know.
When you're under stress
and feeling in a weak state,
the temptation that
plays into your weakness
is right in front of you.
And it's tempting.
So I think I'm gonna take the job.
You haven't worked for like
the last couple months.
I was dealing with the wedding.
You're gonna take a job
while we're here?
That's rude. No.
Shane has an expectation that's like,
"I have all the money,
and I provide this lifestyle.
And the thing you provide
is to shut up and go along with it."
Shane feels all relationships
are a deal,
and in this regard,
this is a great deal.
Everyone gets what they want.
And all she has to do is enjoy it.
I don't know,
I hate to like blow your mind,
but your situation has changed.
You don't need to do anything anymore,
now you just do what you want to do,
and whatever that is.
Shane thinks
that he views his wife as an equal,
he thinks he's wonderful to her
and he's not listening to her problems
because he just doesn't understand
her problems.
Because, for him,
I'm hysterical about the fact
that I can't make
200 dollars writing hack-job articles
that are clickbait.
But, for me, that's my entire career
and that's my entire life.
The scene starts where Nicole
is actually very flattered
that this young woman admires her,
and is seeking her advice.
And those are all things
that enflame Nicole's
ego and all of the things
that she values about herself.
I just wanted to say that I admire you.
As a woman, it's really...
it's inspiring.
She's reaching out
to this woman who's accomplished,
for encouragement.
And the turn is hilarious,
because essentially
I get completely shut down
and it becomes
a very negative experience.
I actually...
I wrote a profile about you.
"Ten Power Women in the Tech World."
Yeah, I remember that.
That was a hatchet job.
Hey!
Quinn spends a lot of time with his dad
in the show.
He is talking all the time
and I say very few words.
Every day sort of spinning
a new epiphany.
I thought I had cancer.
We've got to make the most
out of every moment.
Let's mix it up, let's bro out, come on!
Time is valuable, and generationally,
you have to look at fathers
and the way that they change.
He speaks to being raised by a dad
who's so private with his life
and didn't do any of the parenting.
So now suddenly,
you have a father
who was raised that way
and is trying to actually step in,
and doesn't really know
his own responsibility.
Is that a water bong?
- Uh, we found it on the beach.
- It's prescription.
Paula finds Olivia's parents
to be out-of-touch,
and a couple that
benefits from privilege.
And that's something that,
after a while,
starts to rub Paula the wrong way.
Most people admire people
who achieve things,
but you somehow look at it
as if it's a personality disorder.
What exactly are you getting done?
Putin is an over-achiever.
He's impressive, also evil.
- Liv, you mother is not Putin.
- Thank you.
Creating this duality within Paula,
where she could exist
in a wealthy, upper-class,
homogenous space.
But, really, at the end of the day,
not being accepted.
And that's why she starts
to connect with someone else
while she is on vacation
with Olivia's family.
White Lotus is making a comment
about wealth and privilege.
Some of these problems
that these people have,
these are problems with solutions,
just seems very difficult
to the characters.
_